[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Greek prefix anthro refer to?", "correct_answer": "Mankind", "incorrect_answers": ["study of", "Science", "Sameness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what percentage of a jellyfish is water ?", "correct_answer": "95", "incorrect_answers": ["98", "90", "85"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who placed the bomb at the headquarters of Bonds Russian ally in The World Is Not Enough?", "correct_answer": "Bullion", "incorrect_answers": ["Renard", "Arkov", "Davidov"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most important sense for raccoons?", "correct_answer": "Sense of touch", "incorrect_answers": ["Vision", "Sense of smell", "Hearing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements about AIDS is true?", "correct_answer": "You cant get AIDS from a mosquito bite.", "incorrect_answers": ["AIDS can be transmitted through casual contact with an HIV-positive person.", "You cant get AIDS through oral sex.", "HIV does not actually cause AIDS."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Dead Presidents, what was the last name of Anthonys girlfriend, Juanita?", "correct_answer": "Benson", "incorrect_answers": ["Taylor", "Smith", "Miller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zac Efron made his acting debut in High School Musical.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is sometimes used to refer to perfumers, the experts who compose perfumes?", "correct_answer": "Nez", "incorrect_answers": ["Brez", "Pez", "Trez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tom Hanks character in Forrest Gump was selected to run back kickoffs for the University of Alabama but on his first try, he ran the wrong way for safety.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which three nations have not officially adopted the metric system?", "correct_answer": "The USA, Liberia, Myanmar", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA, Jamaica, Libya", "The USA, the United Kingdom, Malawi", "The USA, Jamaica, Burma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Rosenbergs, who were convicted of conspiracy, were held at what prison?", "correct_answer": "Sing Sing", "incorrect_answers": ["Folsom", "Alcatraz", "Attica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character in The Benchwarmers is the local billionaire, portrayed by Jon Lovitz.", "correct_answer": "Mel", "incorrect_answers": ["Ryan", "Gus", "Tom"]}]